{
	"quiz": [{

		"setId": "1",
		"setone": [{
				"id": "1",
				"question": "1 - When will the world end?",
				"answer": "A"
			},
			{
				"id": "2",
				"question": "2 - When will the world end?",
				"answer": "B"
			},
			{
				"id": "3",
				"question": "3 - When will the world end?",
				"answer": "C"
			},
			{
				"id": "4",
				"question": "4 - When will the world end?",
				"answer": "D"
			},
			{
				"id": "5",
				"question": "5 - When will the world end?",
				"answer": "E"
			}

		]


	},
	{

		"setId": "2",
		"settwo": [{
				"id": "1",
				"question": "1 - When will the world end?",
				"answer": "F"
			},
			{
				"id": "2",
				"question": "2 - When will the world end?",
				"answer": "G"
			},
			{
				"id": "3",
				"question": "3 - When will the world end?",
				"answer": "H"
			},
			{
				"id": "4",
				"question": "4 - When will the world end?",
				"answer": "I"
			},
			{
				"id": "5",
				"question": "5 - When will the world end?",
				"answer": "J"
			}

		]

	
	}]
}
